(Leonard:)So is that it?
Are we engaged?
(Penny:)Yeah, I think so.
(Raj:)All right.
(Penny:)What's wrong?
(Leonard:)I'm not sure.
Just... feels a little anticlimactic.
(Penny:)Yeah, it kind of does, huh?
(Leonard:)Oh, I know.
(Leonard:)This might help.
(Penny:)Where did you get a ring?
(Leonard:)I've... had it for a couple years,
not important.
(Leonard:)Penny... will you marry me?
(Penny:)Oh, my God, yes.
(Leonard:)This would have been
so much more romantic
(Leonard:)if you didn't have
monkey hair on your finger.
(Howard:)How you feeling?
(Bernadette:)Last night was a little rough,
but I think we're gonna get through this.
(Howard:)I'm proud of us.
(Wil:)Me, too.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Where's my pancakes?
Coming, Mrs. Wolowitzl
(Bernadette:)-You were right.
-Welcome to Team Putz.